beachhouse.com 2012-11-19

# Privacy Policy

### 1\. what this privacy policy covers

This Privacy Policy covers Beachhouse.com®'s treatment of personally identifiable information that Beachhouse.com collects when you are on the Beachhouse.com site, and when you use Beachhouse.com's services. This policy also covers Beachhouse.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Beachhouse.com's business partners share with Beachhouse.com or that Beachhouse.com may collect on a partner's site. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Beachhouse.com does not own or control, or to people that Beachhouse.com does not employ or manage.

### 2\. information collection and use

Beachhouse.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Beachhouse.com account, when you use certain Beachhouse.com products or services, when you visit Beachhouse.com pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Beachhouse.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 

When you register with Beachhouse.com, we may ask for various items of personal information, including but not limited to your name, address, zip code, telephone numbers, fax numbers, e-mail addresses, birth date, gender, marital status, occupation, industry, personal interests. Once you register with Beachhouse.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

Beachhouse.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Beachhouse.com cookie information and the page you requested. 

Beachhouse.com may use information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

### 3\. information sharing and disclosure

Beachhouse.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Beachhouse.com may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

We have your consent to share the information; We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Beachhouse.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Beachhouse.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

### 4\. cookies

Beachhouse.com may set and access cookies on your computer. Beachhouse.com may allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

### 5\. Behavioral Advertising

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

### 6\. Changes to this privacy policy

Beachhouse.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
